ebonbrowser.com 2016-09-18

# EbonMedia

Your privacy is important to us. Ebonmedia Corp. ("Ebonmedia") provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from you when you use the Ebon browser, the Ebon website and various other Ebon services. Together, we refer to the browser, website, and services as "Ebon"). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that is provided to us through Ebon. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Ebon website. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes.

## General Terms

It is not necessary for you to provide any personally identifiable information in order to use Ebon browser.

## PII Collection

When you communicate with us or use Ebon in different ways (social networking, etc.), we may collect personally identifiable information about you. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. For instance, if you email us requesting support, you'll provide us with your email address so we can respond to you. Personal Information can also include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, or home address. (We might not ask you for all or any of these things, but you might provide them to us without our asking – for instance, in an email to us.) We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Services and to respond to your requests for support.

## How We Use Your Information

We don't sell your Personal Information. We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) to provide you with better services and improve Ebon, and to respond to your requests for support. Your Non-Identifying Information, such as device ID's and profile information can be made available by Ebon and its partners to help target ads to you. This is all non-identifying information which you agree to share when you download any of the Ebon applications.

## Collecting Information for Third Parties

Ebonmedia helps to collect some statistical data for such services like [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/?utm_expid=71218119-7.lBgmrTO8R3uEDwsxNxa_Nw.0&utm_referrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2Fanalytics%2F), [Alexa.com](http://www.alexa.com/) and [SimilarWeb](http://www.similarweb.com/). This means that by using Ebonbrowser or other Ebonmedia’s services you give us your consent to use your NON-PII for improving analytical services listed above. You can read more about these services and what information do they collect here:

  * <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/>;
  * <http://www.alexa.com/help/privacy>;
  * <http://www.similarweb.com/privacy-policy>

If our policy is not acceptable to you, your only option is to stop using the Software and uninstall it from any computers on which you have it installed.

## NON-PII collection/storage

Ebon browser collects anonymous non personal information, including, but not limited to: cookies, browser language and versions data, IP and MAC addresses, geolocation data, browser history. This information may be used by us and shared with Ebon browser Partners in order to better serve your needs and provide you with relevant content and advertisement. Among the kinds of information we track, without limitation, are the following.

  * Which Ebon features you use and how often (for instance, how often you use the privacy button, share button, search feature, etc.); 
  * The amount of time that Ebon runs and the amount of time it is active;
  * Ebon crashes and associated conditions around the time of the crash;
  * What you've selected for certain Ebon preferences and options;
  * Which other Internet browsers run on your system, and which browser is set as the default browser; If you choose to use it as default browser, Ebon will automatically import existing preferences, bookmarks, history, passwords, cookies and favorites from your current browser for your convenience 
  * Your screen resolution, operating system version, CPU and memory configuration of your machine, and other configuration information; 
  * The number of tabs you have open;
  * Which partners and pages you visit so we can better tailor and offer you customized rewards;

## Log Data

When you visit the Ebon Website (like [www.ebonbrowser.com](http://www.ebonbrowser.com/)), whether you're using Ebon, or as a non-registered user just visiting, our servers automatically record information your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This data is collected whether or not you use Ebon, but only when you visit our website. This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to our Sites, pages of our websites that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our websites, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the websites and the Service and for the websites technical administration, to increase our websites functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors' needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the websites meet the criteria required to process their requests. 

## Aggregating Information

We may aggregate the Non-Identifying Information we collect with similar information collected from other Ebon Users to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of Ebon, and to analyze and understand how Ebon is used. We may also use information you provide without aggregating it to serve you specifically; for instance, to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

## Marketing

We also may use your Personal Information to contact you with Ebon newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you, if you agreed to receive such information. If you decide at any time you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

## COLLECTION, USE, AND RETENTION OF NON-PII 

We collect non-PII on our website using cookies, web beacons, and tags for the operation of the site (e.g. managing user sessions), including analyzing site usage, detecting and preventing malicious behavior on the site, and improving the content and organization of the site. We also engage other companies that will use similar methods to collect non-PII on our website for analyzing site usage. By agreeing to use Ebonbrowser and it's services provided by Ebonbrowser's Partners you hereby agree to Partner's Privacy Policy. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. Ebonmedia cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties that we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal processes (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Ebonmedia or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable. 

## Security

Ebonmedia is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Although Ebonmedia cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Ebonmedia has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email, Facebook message, or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

## Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. Ebonmedia operates its website and browser in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). The Ebon is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that such individuals do not provide any personally identifying information through the Ebon website. 

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@ebonbrowser.com](mailto:privacy@ebonbrowser.com)

## Mail Address

_Ebonmedia Corp._

_Krisjana Valdemara iela 21-20, Riga, LV-1010,Latvia._
